Upcami
Here we go, up-cami. This time I'll be talking with Morning Musume。 23Mariaki Makino and
23 and Akane Matsumoto of Angulum.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
Now then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs.
I, Mariaki Makino, would like to talk about our performance at the Rock in Japan Festival 2023.
The other day, I had the opportunity to perform at Morning Musume。 14, and during the live performance, water was supplied for some reason,
During the live, for some reason, I couldn't drink water at the water supply timing.
It was an important time to drink water.
The concert lasted for 40 minutes, and they prepared water for us to drink,
I was too hot and my head was foggy,
I wandered around and thought, "Oh, I should drink water, but I don't know how to drink water from this cap, so I'll stop.
I didn't think it through properly, and for some reason, I didn't drink the water.
I thought it was hot, but I managed to wait until the end.
It was quite a happening for me, so I whined to the members that I couldn't drink water.
I was like, "Oh, no, you didn't! I was a little bit upset. But it was a lot of fun, and I really appreciate those who came.
I'm glad we could do it safely. Thank you very much. If you don't drink water, it will be hard work for about 40 minutes, right? That's right. Shigeru Matsumoto, did you drink the water? Did you drink water properly? I was able to drink it. I'm glad. Yes, I'm glad.
This was the first festival after Akari Takeuchi's graduation,
The weather was rain or shine, so we rehearsed and thought about what we would say if it was raining, and what we would say if it was sunny.
I see. But it was a sunny version, right? Yes. I'm glad we were able to do the sunny version.
After Angstrom had finished, Morning Musume。 After Angstrom finished, Morning Musume went backstage for their performance,
After Angstrom finished, Morning Musume went to the back of the stage for their performance, and I could feel their passion in their answers.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Now, let's start with this time's up-date.
Tea Horse, A Little Emotionally Unstable Summer Dance Lesson
Here is the dance lesson of "Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer" from the latest single of Tea Horse.
Please take a look at the dance lesson of "Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer" from the latest single of Tea Horse.
Yes. Emotionally Unstable
Oh! she said.
Ups and downs...
Emotionally unstable
Yes. So I'll give it a try.
The Holy Night Era of Summer
I'm upping the ante.
Whose Holy NightWhose Holy Night
He's making it up.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
You're the type of guy whose good humor comes out in the wind.
Six inches above the earth.
You may think you're dressed up, but it's not.
Your ideal time. It's changing all the time.
Okay, next.
Pampas are with you.
Ready, go!
N, ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta
N, takanta, n, takanta, n, takanta
You're the low man here.
Let me make this a little clearer.
Let's see.
The top one...
Yeah.
Next.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la.
Overacting.
Yeah, here it comes.
Here we go.
Dan, here's another version you can play.
Ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah.
Yeah, poof.
Pow.
Sorry.
I think I'm gonna put all my hands here, too.
I'm looking.
I'm looking at you.
Let's go for a second look.
I'm watching you.
Third time, I'm watching you.I'm looking at it for the third time.
Mm-hmm.
Ooh-ohh.
It's popping.
Pappa spel.
You don't even have to have each one here.
pop
yes
Let's do it.
Let's be messy
Yes, we can each make a messYes, I'll make it fun
I'll make it exciting.
I'm going in before Hiromoto.
Okay, okay, change it up.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Delusional dolima.
Okay, okay, okay.
You don't have to leave your body here, you can just keep going in the direction you're going.
I'm going in the direction I'm going.
Tsutsui's scene.
Ready?
Delusional dolima!
Boom, boom, boom!
Oh, wait, I want to change something.
When I changed to Tashiro.
I was turning in the direction of travel.
I'm low in front, but
Front.
Here we go.
Let's go!Seino
Delusional dolima
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
Yeah, come on.
A lifetime full of tension
what the hell is going on?
Sau
Natsu no
Backward
One more time!
Keep the triangle close to the person behind you
Natsu's first
Natsu'sYes, stay behind me
Ishikari, stay close
all the way, all the way
Change
We're already in two rows here.
Up and down, up and down, up and down.
Inside is up.
Up, up, up, up, up.
We'll start at the end.
Yes, sir.
Up, up, up, up, up.
Open your body.
On the ground.
Up and down and up and down
Hands in front
Feet and legs and
Up and down and up and down
On the ground
Low.
I've got it!
I'm so proud of myself!
That's right, tears are falling. Laughter is breaking out.
I can feel the way you're looking at me.I can feel it too, the way you're looking at me.
When I see it, I smile, and it makes me feel a little better.
You're smiling even though I'm fluttering.
Nakayama!
Let's go in together... just the two of us.
Hiromoto and Nakayama... but everyone came right away.
I was watching Hiromoto with the engine.
I was watching Hiromoto.
I don't feel like being delusional right now.
What's going on?
It's summer... summer... summer... summer... summer...
Tara-tara-tara-tara-tara-tara-tara-tara!
Tara-tara-tara, triangle keepTatara-tatara Tatara engine
Tatara-tatara two rows
Tatara Tatara from 2
More and more U Down Down
Up Down Down Up Backward
Summer, this is also up and down.
Okay, ready? Let's hear a little sound.
Yes.
I wonder if it's Natsu's fault.
Whose fault is it?
It's a little unstable.
I'll try my best.
You have one minute to see how it comes out.
Six centimeters from the earth
Overflowing
Oh, oh, oh
I thought I was talking to you
But it's all just a big fat mess.
Ah Never again
Tonight I'm waiting for you
Oh Oh Oh
A chorus of emotionsEmotional Chorus
I don't know if it's similar
I'm gonna regret this for a minute.
I don't know if it's the summer, or if it's just a dream
I don't know if it's the summer, or if it's a dream, but just a little bit.
I don't know who's to blame I'll leave you to it Goodbye play now
The sun's shining, the petals are falling all over the place
The sun's been beating down, the petals are all messed up
Summer skies, whims and fancies
# Believe in me, I've got it, growing up insecure #
Steady summer fall, summer day.
I think it's the height of the moon that I like.
You ask, so I'll answer seriously.
I'm sorry, but my all-time favorite thing is...
I've been wanting to make an appeal to youI'm waking up to your words and I'm glowing
I'm stepping around the corner
I can see the lights
I can feel your eyes on me without even thinking
I'm going to play it softly
I'll make an appointment and make it exciting
me
We had a dance lesson for "Emotionally Unstable Summer," and as the title suggests, there is a part of us that is emotionally unstable, so please pay attention to our facial expressions.
I hope you can pay attention to the expressions on their faces, such as anxious, smiling, etc., so you can see their various expressions of instability.
And the choreography is also very much in line with the lyrics, so I'd be happy if you could see a lot of the choreography.
I was looking forward to seeing the music video, which was written by Kamie Hirose, so I watched it on the day it was released.
Yes, I saw it too.
Yes, I saw the music video on the day it was released.
Yes, it looks like fun. Fireworks and stuff.
I was happy that I could see the process of the choreography.
Yes, that's right. The lyrics and the dances are pretty much linked, so I could see everyone's expressions and so on.
I thought it was very cute.
It's cute.
It makes you want to imitate them.
Please watch the music video.
That's all for now, a slightly unstable summer dance lesson in the rain of tea.These were tea rains and a slightly emotionally unstable summer dance lesson.
I won't kiss the winning Levenchover.
Even you have to take it from me.
Juice Juice PRIDE BRITE
Now on sale
Here is the next one. Angelem Doukou student vocal recording
Here is the vocal recording of Akari Takeuchi from Angulum's latest single!
2, 2, um, yes, 2, 2, yes, yes, yes, yes, please!
Thank you very much.
Like that girl, I'm sure everyone looks better than me
I don't show it when I play.
You look better.
Yes, sir.
Like her, I'm sure everyone looks better than me
They don't show it when they playYou're kind. You're kind.
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, sir.
The part where he sings with more passion than I thought he would...
I was struggling to remember the song.
I was struggling to remember.
I was trying hard to remember what he used to do.
The atmosphere of Ange's songs were totally different.
I guess it was a different part of the song, and the way it sounded rhythmic.
I struggled a little bit with the way the rhythm sounded.
I struggled a little bit.
I couldn't do it.
Yes, I am.
Yes, sir.
No way
Yes, I love you
I love you I'm sorry I doubted you
I love you I know how happy you are
I know how happy you are
Dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dahDah-dah-kah.
Dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah.
Dakdakkaa.
Yes, sir.
Here you go.
I've got something for you.
You let me meet you?
I love you
I'm sorry I doubted you
I've been so happy.
I know how happy you are
I know you were happy
I know you're happy, you idiot. I know you're happy.
The rhythm of the song is the most important thing.
That's what we did for this song as a whole.It's totally different from our usual songs.
I struggled with the rhythm and the cutting part.
It had been a long time since we last played together.
We'll see each other again.
I see... pickle
I'll see you soon.
Thanks for today. I'll see you again.
This is the last single for me.
I was really happy to get Tsunku's music for the last time.
The recording staff was different from mine.
It reminded me of the old days and made me feel various feelings.
Thank you very much.
This song "Alumni" is your last single.
Tsunku wrote the lyrics, and it was the first time for me to sing a Tsunku song.
He taught me a lot about rhythm in the recording.
He gave me a lot of advice on rhythm, such as cutting off at the third beat and bouncing a little more here and there, but it was very difficult and I struggled.
It was very difficult and I struggled with it.It was very difficult and I struggled with it.
I saw this song live for the first time at Yokohama Arena.
It was so cute with the balloons.
I felt like it was the old S/mileage song.
But I could feel the good vibe of the current Angstrom from the alumni.
It became my favorite song too!
I'm so happy, thank you!
And I can't stop listening to Takeuchi-san's recording.
I'm so happy to hear your voice again!
Thank you very much!
That's all for the vocal recording of Angulum alumna Akari Takeuchi!
It's been a while. Thanks for watching.
This is Akane Matsumoto of Angelem with an up-dated paper. Next up is Morning Musume。 23 new member's first recording
Morning Musume。' 23 new members, Haruka Inoue and Akane Yumegeta, are going to record their new album "Morning Musume。
Morning Musume。 Best Selection THE 25th Anniversary, which will be released on August 30.
Please take a look at this. 23's Haruka Inoue.
Morning Musume。's Best Selection' The 25th Anniversary, which was released on August 30. Best Selection' The 25th Anniversary, which was released on August 30.
I say I'm going out, but I don't go out.
I made excuses for not going out, and I was slow in preparing.
Recording was something I had never done before.
I was more excited about how it would turn out than nervous.
I made excuses for being late in preparing.
Unspeakable pots and pans and doodle-doodle-doodle-doodle-doodle-doodle-doodle-doodle-doodle-doodle.
I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know.
Your mother apologized to me...
I've been having a lot of trouble
I was enjoying singing the chorus.
But in the B melody, I was talking too fast
I tended to take notes too fast.
I tried not to sing too fast.
Your mother apologized to me.
Rudeness
I can't imagine what the future holds
Without me, it's all over
I'm the only one who knows what he's talking about
Ramblingsdisorder in which a person is left with an unresolved conscience
I'm riddled with regret.
I'm drunk on myself, too.
I'm a genius at spoiling people
Wow wow yeah yeah
I'm gonna go to the big parce
You're the one who's always there
I'm so excited
We're going out
Rashidness
The hardest part was talking too fast.
You know, like when you're talking too fast, or when you're taking notes too fast.
I would take them out.
I had to chew a lot.
I thought it was difficult, but
I tried my best to fix it.
I worked hard on the recording.
The song is included in Morning Musume。 Best Selection The 25th Anniversary, which was released on August 30.
It was the recording for the Minamiyama Award and Shoyama Award
Haruka Inoue was recording for the first time, so I was a little nervous watching her.
Haruka is a very good singer and there are many things I'm looking forward to.
I'm looking forward to seeing the recording video.
The Minamiyama Award and Shoyama Award were also given to Morning Musume。 It's been a while since we've had such a cute song from Morning Musume.
The words "Let's go to a big parfait" are so cute by themselves, but when I listened to the song, it was so cute from the beginning to the end.
But if you listen to the song, it's cute from beginning to end.
There are parts that sound like lines, so I would like you to pay attention to those parts as well.
I thought it was really cute how she kept her hands in front of her when she sang.
I also thought the way she sang with her beautiful endings made me want to listen to more and more of her songs.
That's all for Morning Musume。 23 new member Haruka Inoue's first vocal recording.
To be continued
Thank you for your work!
This is Maria Makino and Wakana Matsumoto's up-page report.
It's time to say goodbye!
We've been watching a lot of videos this time...
I, Matsumoto, saw the vocal recording of Akari Takeuchi's alumnae.
Since she graduated so abruptly recentlyI've recently graduated suddenly.
I was very happy to see her voice on the recording.
I was very happy to be able to see Takeuchi's voice on the recording, and
Alumni" was a song that I personally struggled with
I was glad to see how you sang it like this.
I, Maria Makino, was looking forward to seeing Haruka Inoue's first recording
I was so happy to see it.
I'm looking forward to performing with you in the future.
And the slightly emotionally unstable summer dance lesson of Tea Horse
Yoshiko-sensei's cute choreography!
I'm looking forward to seeing them in many more concerts!
UpCami takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UpFront Group.
We'll be showing you what you can't see, so please subscribe to our channel!
Please subscribe to our channel!
This time upcami is with Morning Musume。 23 Maria Makino and
Waka Matsumoto of Angulum.
Good bye.
Next time on Upkami, we'll have Morning Musume。 23's new member, Limigaitako's first recording.